♪ D-J Khaled ♪
(upbeat hip-hop music)
♪ Hey, yeah ♪
♪ We the best ♪
♪ All I do is win, win,
win no matter what ♪
♪ Got money on my mind
I can never get enough ♪
♪ And every time I step
up in the buildin' ♪
♪ Everybody hands go up ♪
♪ And they stay there ♪
♪ And they say yeah ♪
♪ Up down, up down, up down ♪
♪ Cause all I do is win, win, win ♪
♪ And if you goin' in put
your hands in the air ♪
♪ Make 'em stay there ♪
♪ Luda ♪
♪ Ludacris goin' in on the verse ♪
♪ Cause I never been defeated
and I won't stop now ♪
♪ Keep your hands up get 'em
in the sky for the homies ♪
♪ That didn't make it and
the folks locked down ♪
♪ I never went no where ♪
♪ But they saying Luda's back ♪
♪ Blame it on that Conjure ♪
♪ The hood call it Luda-Yac ♪
♪ And I'm on this foolish track,
so I spit my foolish flow ♪
♪ My hands go up and down
like strippers booty's go ♪
♪ My verses still be serving,
tight like a million virgins ♪
♪ Last time on a Khaled remix ♪
♪ Now I'm on the original version ♪
♪ Can't never count me out ♪
♪ Y'all better count me in ♪
♪ Got twenty bank accounts,
accountants count me in ♪
♪ Make millions every year,
the south's champion ♪
♪ Cause all I do, all I, all I, all I ♪
♪ All I do is ♪
♪ All I do is win, win,
win no matter what ♪
♪ Got money on my mind
I can never get enough ♪
♪ And every time I step
up in the buildin' ♪
♪ Everybody hands go up ♪
♪ And they stay there ♪
♪ And they say yeah ♪
♪ Up down, up down, up down ♪
♪ Cause all I do is win, win, win ♪
♪ And if you goin' in put
your hands in the air ♪
♪ Make 'em stay there ♪
♪ Swerving in my lo-lo ♪
♪ Head on the swivel ♪
♪ You know serving me's a no no ♪
♪ Clean as a whistle as I
pull out in my Rolls Royce ♪
♪ Yellow bone passenger they
see it, they say oh boy ♪
♪ Tell Khaled back it up,
my niggas call me Loco ♪
♪ Down for armed trafficking,
don't make me pull that fo, fo ♪
♪ Ask you what you laughing at ♪
♪ Represent that mud life ♪
♪ Mud life ♪
♪ Dirty money bitch you better ♪
♪ Get your mug right ♪
♪ Mug right ♪
♪ We come together holding hands ♪
♪ And holla thug life ♪
♪ Thug life ♪
♪ We all strapped in all black ♪
♪ It's like fuck life ♪
♪ All we do is win ♪
♪ You riding or what, what ♪
♪ Cause we riding tonight, night ♪
♪ Now she riding with me cause
you wasn't ridin' her right ♪
♪ All I do is win, win,
win no matter what ♪
♪ Got money on my mind
I can never get enough ♪
♪ And every time I step
up in the buildin' ♪
♪ Everybody hands go up ♪
♪ And they stay there ♪
♪ And they say yeah ♪
♪ Up down, up down, up down ♪
♪ Cause all I do is win, win, win ♪
♪ And if you goin' in put
your hands in the air ♪
♪ Make 'em stay there ♪
♪ Heat in the kitchen, pot on the stove ♪
♪ Water getting boiled, dope being sold ♪
♪ Snoopy in the hoopty, system overload ♪
♪ I've been runnin' this rap game ♪
♪ Since I was twenty years old ♪
♪ I hung with the worst of 'em ♪
♪ Bust till I burst on 'em ♪
♪ Floss 'em up, toss 'em
up, Hardaway, cross 'em up ♪
♪ Pardon me I'm bossin' up,
pressure up, bless ya bruh ♪
♪ Don't mess with us ♪
♪ We like the "U" in the 80's ♪
♪ Back to back set a trap ♪
♪ Hit the lick, get it back ♪
♪ Hit the trick, jump the track ♪
♪ Bitch I want my money back ♪
♪ Time and time again while
I'm sipping on this gin ♪
♪ Al Davis said it best,
just win baby win ♪
♪ All I do is win, win,
win no matter what ♪
♪ Got money on my mind
I can never get enough ♪
♪ And every time I step
up in the buildin' ♪
♪ Everybody hands go up ♪
♪ And they stay there ♪
♪ And they say yeah ♪
♪ Up down, up down, up down ♪
♪ Cause all I do is win, win, win ♪
♪ And if you goin' in put
your hands in the air ♪
♪ Make 'em stay there ♪